Hello. I'm Tristan Martin.

G: github.com/TristanDMartin W: tristandmartin.com E: tristanmartin88@gmail.com P: 404.465.0563.

Web Developer(Designer) & UX Designer with a 3 years of experience. Seeking to enhance my skill in Web design. Recently, I sharpened up my Front End design by completing the Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp at Rutgers University where I developed my skills in HTML, CSS, Project Management and Javascript. I strive to give my customers an amazing experience in UX and Front End Design.

Skills



- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- APIs
- Social Media Strategy
- Brand Management
- JavaScript
- SquareSpace
- GitHub

Tools



- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe After Effects
- Microsoft Suite
- Google Workspace
- Trello
- Mac Proficient

Education



2019 | CODING CERTIFICATE

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Rutgers University, Jersey City, NJ

2017 | APPLE CERTIFICATE

APPLE CERTIFIED IOS TECHNICIAN

Apple Authorized Service Provider, Kalamazoo, Mi

2010 | ASSOCIATE DEGREE

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Gwinnett Tech, Lawrenceville, GA

Experience



2020 - PRESENT

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER

MWNY | New York, NY |

MWNY specializes in execution and realization of brand packaging innovations, my role is to design & develop the web presence for a new look and feel of MWNY.

- Designing a new website layout from the ground up using Squarespace.
- Developed a series of templates in photoshop so client has choices between designs.

12-2020 - 01-2021

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER

JSTORM2594 | JERSEY CITY, NJ | https://jstormshelter.com/

Website developed for twitch streamer J-storm he wanted to revamp his Outreach to new followers on twitch, Developed a website using tools to optimize the website.

- Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, and bootstrap.
- Built a web application from start to finish.
- Maintained applications and updated them for connection to Godaddy SSL & Domain.
- Able to identify problems and bugs in the code and quickly resolved them.

07-2020 - 09-2020

FREELANCE WEB DESIGNER

BAJA CALI FITNESS | JERSEY CITY, NJ | https://www.bajacalifitness.com/

Building a Fitness website to improve the clients Reach to existing members and newcomers.

- Layout design then implemented on Squarespace.
- Resized and formatted Images on Photoshop.
- Made a Blog feature for client to update to their community.

Applications Built



2019

CDADHI

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/TRISTANDMARTIN/GRAPHY | HTTPS://GRAPHY1.HEROKUAPP.COM/

website developed for clients that purchased Stocks and wanted to know how news articles affected the Stock market.

- Web Developer: Wireframe and layout design then implemented the widgets into the website. Also, I designed the color theme and feel of the webpage.
- Utilizes: HMTL5, CSS3, Stock market widgets, MySQL, Heroku, JQuery, Express